First and 10 on the New York 32. Malone hands off for a one-yard gain.
首次触地后 马龙一个手传球推进了一码
Can't establish their running game because Washington...
可没能发起快攻，因为华盛顿…
- God will help you. - God owes me a quarter pound.
- 上帝会保佑你的 - 让上帝给我个汉堡包吧
Mince and mash the garlic into a paste.
把大蒜切碎捣烂制成大蒜泥
- I seek... - Go, Buster, go!
- 我在找… - 跑，小鬼，快跑！
- Reputed crime boss Gaitano Cesare...
被称为黑帮教父的盖塔・切萨雷
...once again avoided prison when a mistrial was declared today...
再次免于牢狱之灾 根据《诈骗影响和腐败组织法》
...in his eight-week long RICO prosecution.
发起的长达8周的起诉，今天被驳回
Allegedly responsible for over 200 murders...
切萨雷被控对多达200起谋杀负有责任
...Cesare has yet to spend one day behind bars.
他明天就会被释放
Mr. Eugene Gordlock...
尤金・葛洛克先生
...a witness who repeatedly asked the judge to be recused from the case...
一个此前屡次要求法官回避此案的证人
...was gunned down just a few hours earlier.
几小时前被枪杀
We had the opportunity to speak with Mr. Gordlock's mother.
我们获准采访了葛洛克的母亲
They shot him right in our front yard.
他们从我家前院开枪
My dear, sweet little boy.
我可怜的孩子
The pained words of a grieving woman...
可怜母亲的哭泣
...left all alone in a city outraged by these developments.
让义愤的市民们感到无能为力
But with no concrete evidence of tampering...
缺乏指证切萨雷行贿的有力证供
...and with Mr. Gordlock now dead...
现在葛洛克也死了
Do I fix your makeup for you?
我有在你补妆时动手动脚么？
- What? - Here's Billy the Beaut.
- 什么？ - 这位是帅哥比利
The captain should have sent me out here with 30, 40 men...
头儿应该给我派上30，40人
...to raze this bloody get-out-of-jail party. Instead, I'm stuck here with you.
铲平这个该死的接风宴而不是 和你杵在这儿
Well, he might come out tonight.
好了，他今晚可能会出现
As a matter of fact, I'm sure he'll show up.
事实上，我肯定他会露面
And what are you gonna do?
那你又能做什么？
I'm gonna bring him in.
把他送进监狱
You know, you kill me, Soap. Let's just say if you can make this happen...
笑死我了，索普，就算你能做到
...why would you?
可为什么要呢？
He does to those bastards...
他对付那群杂种的方法
...what me and you can only fantasize about.
正是我们想做而不敢做的
Ink, keep your nose clean.
尹克，放机灵点
Yeah.
好的
Sure thing, Pops.
放心吧，老大
Hey.
嗨
Look, you know, it's just...
我只是想告诉你
- Take it easy in there, okay? - Nicky, what am I gonna do?
- 待会进去后轻松点，好吗？ - 尼基，你以为我会做什么？
Give the old guy a heart attack?
让那老家伙犯心肌梗塞吗？
- Go on, beat it. - Give me uno minuto.
- 到一边去 - 让我们单独待会
You handled the witness situation perfectly.
你把证人的事处理得非常好
No sweat, Uncle G.
小事一桩，盖叔
- You look great. - The hell I do.
- 你看起来不错 - 简直是受罪
I shit in a bag, for chrissake.
看在上帝的份上 我排泄都得靠那个袋子
Hey, saves you a trip to the can, right?
省得你到处跑，不是吗？
You came to discuss a private matter.
你是来商量一项家族生意的
Down at the docks!
码头生意！
Right. Yeah. Cristu Bulat.
是的，克里斯汀・布拉特
I hear he's a sick fuck. Fresh off the boat.
听说他是个恶心的杂种 是个刚上岸的雏儿
Cristu's bringing in a shipment and he needs a safe port.
克里斯汀有船货要靠岸 他想要个安全的码头
I've arranged for my customs guy Simmons to be on that night.
我已经安排我在海关的人 西蒙斯那晚当值
The union boys'll be there to unload. Our cut's 10 mil.
帮里的小孩们会在那卸货 我们能挣一千万
- We won'T break a sweat. - Ten mil?
- 完全不费劲 - 一千万？
- Fuck's Cristu shipping? - I don'T know.
- 克里斯汀个杂种运的什么？ - 不知道
It's some kind of biological package.
好像是些生物产品吧
A biological package.
生物产品
I fucking knew it.
我他妈就知道
Probably going up to the ragheads in Queens.
准是给皇后区那帮穆斯林的
- Cristu guaranteed it's leaving the city. - We don'T touch that kind of shit.
- 克里斯汀保证不在城里搞事 - 我们不碰那种狗屎
In case your memory's going with your bodily functions...
万一你的记性和你半身不遂的身体一样
...you might remember I'm the top earner here.
我得提醒你，我是家族里最能挣钱的
- I'm not stupid. - Stupid?
- 我可不蠢 - 不蠢？
You're as shithouse crazy as your brother, Loony Bin Jim.
你像个傻B疯子 和你兄弟疯子本・吉姆一个样
I should have had the both of you locked away.
我就该找个地方把你俩都关起来
One more word about my brother, I swear to Christ I'll...
要再提我兄弟，我发誓，我会…
You'll what? You make one move, you greasy fuck.
会怎么样？ 再向前走一步，让你死得难看
Hey, let's just all calm down here, okay?
嗨，都冷静下，好么？
I've put out a big spread out here.
我在外面准备了丰盛的晚宴
So come on, boys, eat up.
去好好享用吧
We're not eating with the old shitbag, understand?
我们不和那个老杂碎一块吃，懂吗？
Pittsy, pour me a drink.
皮特希，给我倒杯酒
What the fuck?
他妈的什么啊？
Pittsy!
皮特希！
Let's go.
我们走
All right, let's split up.
好了，我们分头行动
Shouldn'T we wait for backup?
不等后援么？
Police! Freeze!
警察！不许动！
Listen, Billy Russoti's getting away.
听着，比利・罗塞蒂逃走了
Silver Rover.
银色罗孚车
You might wanna head down to the docks first.
你最好先赶去码头
Shit, that hurts.
见鬼，真痛
- What happened to you? - Your Punisher.
- 你怎么了？ - 你的那个惩戒者
He disarmed me, held me at gunpoint then he stole our damn ride.
他打伤了我，拿枪指着我 然后抢走我们那辆该死的车
- Where were you, huh? - I knew he would come.
- 你跑哪去了，嗯？ - 我就知道他会来
Hey, let me get your statement.
嘿，让我给你做个笔录
Come on, Saffiotti, tell me everything...
来吧，跟我讲讲详细过程
How did it go down, huh?
究竟怎么一回事，嗯？
I'm sorry about your family, Billy.
比利，我对你们家族的不幸深表遗憾
- Well, maybe it's a blessing in disguise. - What?
- 这算是你的恭贺吗？ - 怎么？
It was time for me to take over anyway.
无论如何，现在轮到我掌权了
Thanks to The Punisher, I don'T even get my fucking hands dirty.
感谢惩戒者，甚至都不用脏我的手
Where's your boss, then?
那么，你老板在哪？
- What the fuck's he doing here? - Relax. I asked him to come.
- 该死的，他来这干嘛？ - 放松点，我让他来的
My man. How are you doing?
我的朋友，你还好吗？
- Who the fuck are these finooks? - These are couple of my colleagues.
- 这些他妈的屁精是谁？ - 他们是我的伙伴
They are very, very gifted delivery men.
他们在送货上有很高的天赋
No mountain too high, no river too deep.
世上无难事，只要肯登攀
All right, all right, all right, enough.
好了，好了，够了
- Pittsy, get me some money. - Time to go to work.
- 皮特希，拿点钱给我 - 工作时间到了
We're running low, boss.
我们所剩无几，老板
We picked up 200K from the Lucciano construction site.
不是刚从鲁契亚诺工地提了20万吗？
I had to launder it through the Pussycat Lounge. Like you told me, remember?
照您的吩咐，放到野猫酒吧去漂白了 记得吗？
Well, bring it back tomorrow.
明天把它拿回来
- You got it, boss. - Here.
- 你说了算，老板 - 给你
That's 20 rolls of hundreds, that's a grand each. All counted.
里面有20卷百元钞每卷1千，全点过了
Head for the port, do your thing...
马上去港口，开始做事
...get over the security fence, hand out the money.
想法通过安检把钱派出去
Where are you going?
你他妈去哪？
Would it be all right if I take the roof instead of the door?
我们喜欢走天窗不走门，没问题吧？
- Whatever. - You're a fucking saint.
- 随你便 - 你真他妈是个好人
Hey, what's the matter?
嘿，怎么回事？
Oh, fuck.
操！
What the fuck was that?
他妈的怎么回事？
Agent down. Repeat, agent down. Fuck.
有伙计受伤，重复，有伙计受伤，操！
I'll check it out, boss.
我出去看看，老板
- Pops! - I'll take care of it. You get the guards.
- 老大！ - 我去解决，你去叫警卫
Pittsy!
皮特希！
Fuck, you bastard. Fuck. Fuck you, Castle!
操，你个杂种，操你，卡塞尔！
Come on, Castle!
来吧，卡塞尔！
Fuck you, man! Fuck you, Castle, you fucking...
我操你！操你，卡塞尔，操你
Fuck you, Castle! Fuck! My fucking face!
操你，卡塞尔！操！我他妈的脸！
Pittsy! Pittsy! Pittsy!
皮特希！皮特希！皮特希！
Fuck, my fucking face!
操，我他妈的脸！
Fuck! Pittsy! Pittsy! Pittsy!
操！皮特希！皮特希！皮特希！
There he is!
他在那儿！
Move! Move! Move!
快！快！快！
Up there!
冲上去！
Move!
快！
Fuck!
操！
Up there!
冲上去！
- FBI. Drop your weapons. - Oh, shit. Shit.
- FBI，把枪丢了 - 噢，见鬼，见鬼
You two, up the stairs. Team 1, on me.
你们两个，上楼 第一队跟着我
Don'T move!
不许动！
FBI! Put your weapons down.
FBI！ 把枪放下
We got a live one!
我们找到一个幸存者
Take care of those five yards in every direction.
周围5码动作轻点
Billy the Beaut.
帅哥比利
Yo, you say Billy the Beaut?
哟，你是说帅哥比利？
- Not anymore, huh? - Bring him down, maybe he'll live.
- 再帅不起来了，呃？ - 把他拉出来，兴许还能活
- Wait a minute. - Repeat, Nicholas Donatelli Jr.
- 等一下 - 重复，尼古拉・多纳特里 初级探员
Reach Donatelli's family. Can you ask Miller if...
联系他的家属，问问米勒是否…
The Lord is compassion and love.
耶和华具怜爱之心
Slow to anger and rich in mercy.
不轻易动怒，慈悲为怀
He does not treat us according to our sins...
他赦免了世人的原罪
...nor repay us according to our faults.
不因过错惩罚我们
As parents have compassion on their children...
如慈父般仁爱
...the Lord has pity on those who fear him.
宽恕那些害怕他的人
For he knows of what we are made, he remembers that we are dust.
因为他知道我们是什么做的 他记得我们只是堆尘土
As for us, our days are like grass.
至于我们，生命如同花草
We flower like the flower of the field.
在大地上盛开
The wind blows and we are gone.
然后风把我们带走
And our place never sees us again.
不再受尘世的羁绊
I'm so sorry for your loss.
对你们的不幸，我深表歉意
Thank you.
谢谢
Who compromised Donatelli?
是谁害了多纳特里？
Calm down, Budiansky, it wasn'T anybody's fault.
冷静点，布迪安斯基 这不是谁的错
None of us could foresee Castle opening up hunting season on La Cosa Nostra.
没人想到卡塞尔会对西西里黑帮 大开杀戒
Come on.
拜托
All right, look, Donatelli sent us a message.
听着，多纳特里先前告诉我
Said something big was gonna happen. He asked for Homeland Security.
会有大事发生 他请求国土安全局支援
We ran 24-hour surveillance on Russoti.
所以我们对罗塞蒂实施24小时监控
Just as we're about to find out what is happening, Donatelli got shot.
就在我们快找出真相前 多纳特里被杀了
Believe me, no one is more pissed off than I am.
相信我，没人比我更懊恼
How is it we're not all over Frank Castle?
那为什么还要放任弗兰克・卡塞尔?
Because we have a real national security threat.
因为我们眼下有个关乎国家 安全的现实威胁
And the last time I checked, that tops trying to nab some crazed vigilante.
而上次我关注他时 那个硬汉正试图阻止一起疯狂的私刑
Go.
走了
- Hey.
- 嗨
I'm gonna get this guy, Angie.
我会抓住那个家伙的，安琪
I promise you.
我保证
I heard the bureau was sending a babysitter.
听说局里给我们派了位临时保姆
Liaison.
是联系人
Thirty years on the force, I still don'T know what that word means.
在军队里待了30年 可我还是搞不懂那个词的意思
We have a certain way of doing things here, Special Agent Budiansky.
特别探员布迪安斯基 我们这儿有自己一套行事方式
Like letting mass murderers run free?
比如让血债累累的凶手逍遥法外？
Four years this Punisher's been wreaking havoc.
四年来，这个惩戒者为了泄愤肆意妄为
And you haven'T once caught a break.
可你们没一次能阻止他
I'm waist deep in shit around here as you can plainly see.
就像你现在看到的 我这儿的屁事多得漫了过腰
Your buddies from the bureau told me...
你在局里的伙伴告诉我
...the city is under some kind of terror threat.
这座城市面临恐怖主义威胁
New Yorkers are a bit sensitive about that, if you know what I mean.
纽约人对此很敏感，你懂我的意思
I've got my men trying to find out...
我让我的人试着去调查
...what your colleague came across when he went under.
你同僚死前的遭遇
Maybe if you feds allowed us in on your undercover operations once in a while...
如果你们FBI能偶尔允许我们按 自己的方式，秘密行事
...all of this could have been avoided. - With all due respect, captain...
- 也许这些不幸可以避免 - 恕我冒昧，长官
...that...
你的话
...is bullshit.
完全是扯淡
What if it had been your man lying there?
如果是你们的人躺在那儿
In a pool of his own blood?
血流成河
You Krispy Kreme motherfuckers would be beating down every door in this city.
你们这群狗杂碎 早就冲出去挨家挨户的搜了
Captain.
长官
Captain, you know what?
长官，知道吗？
The Punisher Task Force could use an extra man.
惩戒者专案组也许还缺个人
Room 12.
地下室
The basement.
12室
Agent Budiansky? Did I get that right?
布迪安斯基特工？我说得对吗？
The captain told me you were coming in.
头儿告诉我你要过来
Welcome to The Punisher Task Force.
欢迎来惩戒者专案组
I'm Detective Martin Soap.
我是马丁・索普探员
Pleasure.
幸会
Make yourself at home.
随便坐吧
You have a degree in Behavioral Psychology?
你有行为心理学的学位？
Surprised?
奇怪吗？
That's okay. Most people are.
没什么，很多人都有
So, what do you actually do here?
那么，你这儿具体都做些什么？
Here?
这儿？
This is ground zero.
什么都做不了
I've shadowed his every step for the last five years.
五年来，我一直在关注他的每一次行动
I've documented every murder that fit his profile...
我记录下他的每次行凶
...and I've collected intelligence on all known associates.
我从所有认识的同事那儿收集相关情报
Take a look at this.
看看这个
Six years ago...
6年前
...Frank Castle was a Special Forces instructor.
弗兰克・卡塞尔是特种部队教员
And a simple family man.
一个有家室的普通人
One day, he takes his wife and kids for a picnic...
一天，他带着妻子和孩子外出野餐
...and by chance or fate, depending on which you believe in...
也许是碰巧，也许是命中注定 看你怎么想了
...they witnessed a mob execution.
他们目睹了一起黑帮灭口
When they were discovered...
他们被发现后
But Castle survived.
不过卡塞尔活了下来
Since then, he's been taking down one crime family after another.
从那以后，他就一个接一个的 猎杀犯罪家族
I'm really close, Budiansky.
我已经很接近了，布迪安斯基
Only thing getting in my way is some bad luck.
只是差点运气
But I have a feeling that's about to change.
不过我觉得情况将会改变
You know, I've been waiting for someone like you.
我一直在等一个像你这样的人
Take a look at some of the case files.
你先读读这个案件的档案
Get a lay of the land.
了解下基本情况
I'll get us a pie from Milano's. Best pizza in the city.
我去叫个米兰匹萨，这城里最好的匹萨
Which drawer?
哪个抽屉
- What? - The alleged Punisher murders.
- 什么？ - 惩戒者案子的档案
All of them.
所有都是
What do you want, Micro?
你想说什么，迈克？
You ever heard of jihadi-blogger. Com?
你有听过“jihadi-blogger.com”这个网站吗？
I'm posing as a one-armed Wahhabi warrior...
我用“独臂瓦哈比武士”的ID发帖
...who took a crap in a cave next to Bin Laden.
假装是位孤注一掷的拉登战士
I think I can score you a couple of rocket launchers.
我想我能为你订些火箭发射器
What do you want?
你到底想说什么？
Haven'T seen you in a while.
有段日子没见你了
Brought you some treats.
我给你搞了份大餐
It's gun show season in Virginia. No background checks, no problems.
是维吉尼亚的枪械展上的没有背景检查 绝对没问题
That's too much, Frank.
不用这么多，弗兰克
Call it a retirement package.
当它是多纳特里的退休金吧
I know this thing with the fed is eating you up...
我知道FBI探员的事让你很难过
...but that doesn'T mean you pack up your tent.
但这不意味着你要卷铺盖走人
We all make mistakes, Frank.
所有人都会犯错，弗兰克
You're fighting a war against the assholes...
你对付的是那些钻法律漏洞
...who slip through the raindrops, who get away with it.
法律无法制裁的浑球
In any war, there's collateral damage. You know that.
任何战争都是有间接伤害的
Collateral damage?
间接伤害？
I killed an agent in the field.
我亲手杀死一个特工
One of the good guys.
一个好人
He had a family.
他也有家庭
You didn'T know.
你当时不知道
I fucked up, Micro.
我搞砸了，迈克
Now, please...
现在，请…
...just leave me alone.
让我单独待会儿
Where the fuck's Nicky?
狗日的尼基在哪？
He...
他…
...didn'T make it.
没来
Nicky was a fucking rat.
尼基是该死的条子
For the feds.
FBI的卧底
What about my money?
我的钱呢？
We already went to his place and tore it apart.
我们去了他住所翻了个底朝天
No sign of a safety deposit key or nothing.
没找到保险箱钥匙或者别的什么线索
Does he got any next of kin?
他有直系亲人吗？
- Somebody to carry on the family name? - Yeah.
- 或者谁和他同姓？ - 有的
Something about a wife and a girl.
听说有个妻子和女儿
Good.
很好
Let's look there.
去查查她们
You got it.
这就去
Hey, doc.
嗨，医生
Where you been?
你去哪儿了？
- Am I glad to see you. - Hi, Billy.
- 真高兴见到你 - 嗨，比利
Should've seen those fucking brascioles at the clinic.
你真该去看看诊所里那些欠操的鸡巴
Must have bought their fucking medical degrees off the Internet.
他们肯定是网上买的医学文凭
How did you end up at a free clinic?
你怎么去了个免费诊所
Insurance said I missed a payment.
保险公司说我忘了缴纳费用
Can you fucking believe that?
你能相信他妈的鬼话吗？
Okay. Before we do this...
好吧，在我们开始之前
...I need you to understand the severity of your injuries.
我想让你知道，你的伤势非常严重
You shouldn'T have been able to survive this.
差点就没命了
Well, that's why I'm here, doc.
所以我才来找你，医生
I have the best plastic surgeon in all of New York.
你是全纽约最棒的外科整形医生
Your facial muscles, tendons, bone structure, everything...
你的脸部肌肉，腱肌，脸骨
...was destroyed.
所有组织都被毁坏了
And there wasn'T a single square inch of skin left intact.
更别提没一块皮肤是完好的了
Just take it off already.
那就全部去掉
Okay.
好吧
Let's do this.
我们开始吧
I'm gonna need you to sit forward a little bit.
请你向前坐一点
All right.
好的
Polymers...
聚合填充物
...a few strategically placed alloy plates...
一些起关键支撑作用的合金板
...and just a little bit of horse hide.
还有点马皮
A little bit of what?
一点什么？
I need to talk to my doctor alone.
我要和医生单独谈谈
Yeah. Yeah, of course, Billy.
好的，好的，当然没问题 比利
The fuck's the matter with you? You can'T control yourself?
你他妈怎么回事？就控制下吗？
You know how sensitive he is.
你知道他对此多敏感吗？
I'm sorry, Pops, it's just, I've... Have you ever seen anything so...?
对不起，老大 我只是，只是从没见过这么…
Just shut the fuck up.
混球，给我闭嘴
You okay, boss?
你没事吧，老板？
Much better. Thanks.
好多了，谢谢
I'll be in the car.
我在车里等你
No more distractions.
我们当务之急
We need to focus on my goals.
有两件事
One:
第一：
We need to get my money back.
拿回我的钱
Two, we're gonna get rid of Frank Castle.
第二：干掉弗兰克・卡塞尔
But he took out, like, 30 of us.
可他干掉了我们差不多30个的人
I mean, how are we gonna kill him before he'll kill us?
我是说我们怎么才能在他 杀我们前杀了他？
My brother will take care of that.
我兄弟会搞定他
- Loony Bin Jim? - Shut the fuck up.
- 疯子本・吉姆？ - 闭嘴，混球
His name is James.
他名字是詹姆斯
Not Loony Bin Jim, not LBJ. James.
不是疯子本・吉姆，是詹姆斯
I'm sorry. It's a good idea.
对不起，您说得对
Really, it is.
真的，您说得对
Don'T mind him.
别生气
He doesn'T think before he talks, just like his mother.
他说话从不动脑筋，跟他妈一个样
Sorry about that, Billy.
我很抱歉，比利
Billy is dead.
比利已经死了
From now on...
从现在起
...you call me Jigsaw.
叫我电锯 （注：这个词也有拼图的意思）
He's mine.
他是我的
Hey, Billy, fuck you!
嗨，比利，操你！
Daddy!
爸爸！
How are we doing today, Loony Bin Jim?
今天我们怎么做呢，疯子本・吉姆？
Yummy, yummy.
好吃，好吃
So good.
味道好极了
- What? - Dr. Basner. Open up!
- 谁阿？ - 贝斯纳 医生，开门！
Yes, doctor.
马上来，医生
Billy?
比利？
Is that you?
是你吗？
It is.
这是…
You look fantastic, brother.
你看起来真不可思议，兄弟
Ink, cut these off, now.
尹克，把皮带割断，快点
Pittsy, go open the doors of every other cell...
皮特希，把其他牢房的门全打开
...lead everybody out the front door. - Sure thing, Billy.
- 把所有人带到前门 - 没问题，比利
Jigsaw.
电锯
I'll take care of this guy.
我来对付这个家伙
Oh, no, brother.
噢，不行，兄弟
Fatso's mine.
胖子是我的
Of course.
没问题
I'm gonna get my applesauce back.
我要拿回我的苹果酱
Did you know...
你知道吗
...kidneys and applesauce are a delicacy in Sweden?
在瑞典，苹果酱拌腰子 是道的美味佳肴
Did you know that?
听说过吗？
Yes.
没错
Yummy, yummy, yummy in my tummy, tummy, tummy.
好吃，好吃，好吃，正合我口味
No.
不
What do you say, boss?
老板，你看怎么着？
- Stuff might come in handy. - What for?
- 这玩意迟早用得着 - 做什么用？
Well, in case he starts, you know, not feeling so good.
万一他开始，呃，觉得有些不舒服
I think he's doing just great.
我看他状态挺好
You're in my light.
你挡着的光了
For the next time someone gets in your light.
下次再有人挡着光，你就用这个
Step the fuck away from my little girl.
从我女儿身边滚远点
Mom, that's a dad word.
妈，那是脏话了
Go inside, Grace.
进屋去，格雷斯
You're messing with the wrong family on the wrong day, asshole.
你在错误的时间来了错误的地方，浑球
You, you're...
你，你是…
What are you doing here?
你来这做什么？
What makes you think you could come here?
是什么让你觉得你有资格来这儿？
- You'll scare the girl. - Shut up.
- 你吓着你女儿了 - 闭嘴
Shut your mouth.
闭上你的嘴
- I'm sorry. - I said shut up.
- 我很抱歉 - 我让你闭嘴
What's this?
这是什么？
Something to help out.
一点补偿
No.
不
No, you don'T get to do that.
不可以，你不可以这么做
You don'T get to shoot my husband in cold blood and then stop at the ATM.
你不可以冷血的枪杀我丈夫后 再用钱来补偿
It's for your daughter.
是给你女儿的
This is what you deserve.
这是你的报应
What you did to Nick.
凭你对尼基所作所为
Who punishes you?
又有谁来惩戒你？
He taught you how to shoot.
他教过你如何用枪
A good agent keeps his family safe...
一个好特工应保证家人的安全…
...but he couldn'T always be here.
可他不能时刻守在家人身边
He took you out to the range.
所以他带你去靶场
He showed you what to do.
教你如何射击
This is where you do it.
对着这儿开枪吧
Squeeze...
握紧枪
...don'T pull.
别犹豫
I can'T find my red pen.
我找不到我的红笔
Mom, I need it.
妈，我需要红笔
You take it.
把这个拿走
Is this it, boss?
就是这儿吗，老板？
Yeah.
是的
Nice, brother.
真漂亮，兄弟
- Is it yours? - Not yet.
- 这是你的吗？ - 还不是
Old Cesare used to rent it to screw hookers.
老切萨雷过去把这租给妓女做生意
Let's go inside before I freeze my fucking balls off.
快进去吧，我他妈的蛋都快冻掉了
What's the matter, Billy?
你怎么了，比利？
Just when I think I'm okay...
我以为当我看到镜子里的自己时
...I see my reflection somewhere...
不会有什么感觉
...and I look horrible.
可我的样子实在太可怕了
What has he done to me?
他对我做了什么？
No, no, no, don'T.
不，不，不，别这样
Don'T cry, brother.
别哭，兄弟
Everything is gonna be all right.
一切都会好起来的
I promise you two things:
我向你保证两件事
One, I will find Castle...
1. 我会找出卡塞尔
...and I will kill him slowly and painfully.
慢慢的把折磨死他
And two, you will never, ever have to look at your reflection again...
2. 只要和我在一起，你就再也…
...as long as you're with me.
不会在镜子里看到自己
You're not in Transylvania anymore, Cristu.
你们可不是在特兰西瓦尼亚 （注:今罗马尼亚中部，传说中吸血鬼的故乡）
We don'T talk vampire.
克里斯汀，我们可不讲吸血鬼的鸟语
It's Russian.
这是俄语
My man is concerned.
我的人很关心
If Punisher can do this to your face...
如果惩戒者能这么对待你的脸
...what might he do to our deal?
那会怎么对待我们的生意呢？
The tongue stretches further than most people think.
人的舌头比大多数人估计的要长得多
Ask your man how he's gonna talk that shit...
问问你的人，等我把他舌头 从他嘴里拉出来后
...when I pull it from his mouth.
他还能怎么谈那个狗屎
Enough.
够了
The Punisher is not a problem.
惩戒者不是问题
The docks are mine.
码头是我的
My looks have nothing to do with this.
我的脸是什么样和生意无关
Everybody...
每一个人
...from the local security to international customs is in my pocket.
从当地保安到国际海关都在我掌控之中
Quite frankly, this job doesn'T get done without me.
坦白告诉你，这件事没有我不会成功
My most sincere apologies.
致以我最真诚的歉意
My father always say never insult your host.
我父亲常说客人不应该侮辱主人
Sounds like a reasonable man.
听起来是个讲道理的人
You don'T know of my father.
你根本不了解他
Three days.
3天
It has to be 12 million.
必须给一千二百万
We agree on 10.
我们说好是一千万的
We both know...
我们都知道
...that this biological shit you're bringing in isn'T leaving the city.
你那狗屁生物产品，根本不会远离纽约市
You're selling it to the ragheads in Queens.
你把它卖给皇后区的那帮穆斯林佬
The ports have been crawling with suits from Homeland.
港口已经挤满了国土安全局的便衣
Gonna take a lot of payola to keep it quiet.
我得花更多的钱贿赂
Always knew you'd be a good boss, Billy.
比利，我一直知道你会是个好老板
Thanks, brother.
谢谢你，兄弟
Latin Kings.
拉丁王 （注：纽约的一个黑帮，成员拉丁移民为主）
Let him go, Frank.
放开他，弗兰克
You know this piece of shit?
你知道这狗屎是谁吗？
Ex piece of shit.
那是过去的事了
Yeah.
好得很
He's a regular choirboy.
他现在是个品学兼优的好青年了
- Fuck you, cracker. - Language.
- 去你妈的，白种佬 - 说什么呢！
It's a genius racket.
这是个绝妙的主意
You know how the cops always run those gun buy-backs?
知道警署的枪械回购策略
Except they never work.
为什么从不凑效么？
Because what banger is gonna trust a cop, right?
因为混混们从不相信警察，不是吗？
Well, these drive-by wack jobs, they just love Carlos here.
那种街头火拼的活计 喜欢用的是卡洛斯这种人
They get one look at that ink...
军火贩子只要看眼他的纹身
...and they know he's for real.
就知道他是同道中人
We get the guns off the street to you.
我们就能把枪从街上给你买回来
Never once seen a banger that could quit.
没听过混混还会改邪归正的
Too fucking stupid.
欠揍的蠢货
He's straight, Frank.
他本质是好的，弗兰克
Hey, Mom, Frank's here.
妈，弗兰克来了
He says eat up, huh?
他说你该把这个吃完，好么？
How's she doing?
她怎么样？
Yeah, well.
唉~还算好
As long as she's got her cooking shows, she's good.
只要有烹调节目，她就有知觉
It's the only thing she notices.
这是她唯一在意的事了
But, hey, that's something, right?
不过这也还算不错，对吗？
Listen, l...
听我说，我…
I just came around to tell you that I'm going out of town for a while.
我来是想告诉你，我要出城一段时间
Out of town?
出城？
I'm sorry.
不好意思
I never thought of The Punisher taking a long weekend.
我都不知道惩戒者还要度周末
I'm not planning on coming back.
我不会回来了
So I take it things didn'T go so well at the Donatelli home?
那么，我猜在多纳特里家 事情处理得并不顺利对吗？
Are you aware that Billy Russoti survived?
你知道比利・罗塞蒂还活着吗？
I heard.
我听说了
Let the cops take care of him.
让警察去操心吧
You and I know they got nothing on him.
我们都知道警察对他束手无策
Their hands are tied. This is where The Punisher comes in.
这个时候应该惩戒者出手
This is why I believe in you, why I supported you all these years.
这也是这么多年来我一直相信你 支持你的原因
You want me to tell you when something happens to Mrs. Donatelli?
你要我告诉你，多纳特里夫人 什么时候会出事吗？
That's what's gonna happen.
让我来告诉你会发生什么
You don'T think he's gonna go for revenge?
你不认为他会回来报复吗？
It's not a question of if, it's a matter of when.
这只是时间问题
- Pull a couple of Berettas. - For what?
- 准备一对伯莱塔（手枪） - 干什么用？
Three...
三
...two...
二
...one.
一
Russoti is the last one, then I'm done.
罗塞蒂是最后一个，然后我就退休
From your lips to God's ears.
一言为定
You know where I can find him?
你知道哪能找到他吗？
I don'T have a fix on him.
不知道
You wiped out his associates that are known to me.
你干掉了我的线人
I saw him with some new guys.
我见他又找了些新人
Leader was black, dreadlocks.
领头的是个黑人，有一头的小辫子
Did some acrobatic stuff over the roofs.
在屋顶做些杂技动作
That's Maginty and his urban free-flow gang.
是麦格迪和他的“城市酷跃帮”
He's a mean motherfucker.
他是个卑劣的杂碎
He's on a constant meth high.
整天都嗑着药
Well, come on.
跟我来
You wanna find this guy or not?
你想不想找到那家伙？
You boys play nice.
小伙子们好好干
- I've been looking for you. - Agent Budiansky, take a load off.
- 我一直在找你 - 布迪安斯基特工，坐下来喝一杯
I need to go see Castle. Where do I find him?
我要见卡塞尔，知道哪能找到他吗？
Rats, you know, he just left.
废话，知道么，他刚走
Wait, wait, wait.
等等，等等
You know what I like to do?
知道我喜欢怎么做吗？
I like to sit in my car...
我喜欢坐在车里
...and listen to the CB radio and follow the crime.
听着车载电台，追踪每个案子
We might just run into him. It's never worked for me in five years...
我们也许会碰上他 虽然过去5年从来没碰上
...but I'm not the luckiest guy on the planet, y'know?
可那是因为我不走运，不是吗？
Let's go through the back door.
我们从后门进
Maginty and his boys are planning to hit a convenience store on 45th and 2nd.
麦格迪他们计划打劫45街2#的一家便利店
Suspects are armed and dangerous.
嫌犯持有武器，非常危险
I repeat, suspects are armed and dangerous.
重复，嫌犯持有武器非常危险
Let's do this.
我们过去
Really?
你说真的？
Just drive the car.
快开车
Come on. Come on.
快点，快点
Oh, fuck.
噢，见鬼
Please.
求求你
- Don'T kill me. - Russoti.
- 别杀我 - 罗塞蒂
- Where is he? - Your man, Jigsaw.
- 他在哪？ - 你是说电锯？
I was just with him. He was supposed to give me some dough for a job.
我刚见过他，他本来说好给我报酬的
But turns out...
可现在
...he don'T have any anymore.
他也没有钱了
He forgot he gave a whole bunch to that FBI rat bastard.
他把一大笔钱交给那个该死的FBI卧底
So he went to go see Donatelli's wee bitch to get it back.
所以他去找多纳特里的娘们拿回钱
Something for something.
一样换一样（所以请别杀我）
Mr. Punisher, sir.
惩戒者先生
So when did Donattelli go undercover?
那纳特里什么时候去卧底的？
We were partners in narcotics.
我们以前在毒品调查科是搭档
Unfortunately, most of the blow we confiscated ended up in my nose.
很不幸，我们查获的大多数可卡因 在我鼻子底下消失了
Internal Affairs tried to get Nicky to rat me out.
内务部想让尼基检举我
He wouldn'T.
他拒绝了
So they send him undercover.
所以他们派他做卧底
He's dead because of me.
他的死全是因为我
So you still skiing the old alps?
所以你至今仍然耿耿于怀？
No.
不
That's in the past.
那是过去的事了
- Holy shit. - Shit.
- 天哪，见鬼了 - 见鬼
Drive around, meet me on the other side.
开车绕过去，在另一边碰头
Mommy.
妈妈
Hello, Mrs. Donatelli.
你好，多纳特里夫人
Or will you be calling yourself Miss from now on?
或许叫你小姐更合适
What do you want from us?
你们想要什么？
I'm looking for my money...
我来找我的钱
...which your rat of a husband stole from me.
你那个当叛徒的丈夫从我这儿偷去的
We don'T have it, I swear to God.
不在我们这儿，我对上帝发誓
How about you, sweetcheeks?
那你呢，小甜妞
Would you also like to swear on an imaginary friend?
你也要对那个虚构的朋友发誓么？
Make sure they don'T move.
看着她们
- We'll look for the money. - Hey, kid.
- 我们去找钱 - 小孩，过来
Freeze, asshole!
别动，浑球！
You're under arrest.
你被捕了
Stay out of my way.
别插手我的事
Listen to me.
听我说
Russoti is headed to the Donattelli house.
罗塞蒂正在去多纳特里家的路上
He's probably already there.
也许他已经到了
You have to let me go.
你得让我走
You have the right to shut the fuck up!
你有权闭上你的臭嘴
Mommy.
妈…
Damn it. Cops.
是该死的条子
- Evening, officers. - Is everything okay in there?
- 晚上好，警官 - 里面都还好吗？
No.
不好
Everything is not okay.
简直糟透了
Follow me.
跟我来
Officer.
警官
Oh, no, you don'T.
哦，不，你别想了
Well, well, well.
看看
This day was bound to come sooner or later, wasn'T it?
这一天迟早会到来，不是吗？
Have you heard back from the patrol car?
巡逻车有回话吗？
Soap.
舒布
I tried a couple of times. There was no answer.
我试着联络了好几次，没有应答
Listen, we gotta get out of here before more pigs arrive.
我们得在更多警察来之前赶紧离开
- No! - Where is my fucking money?
- 不要！ - 我的钱他妈的到底在哪？
My husband has a safe upstairs in the bedroom.
我丈夫在楼上卧室有个保险箱
I don'T know if it's there but I can give you the combination.
我不知道在不在那，但我可以给你密码
10-12-19-65.
10-12-19-65
Oh, how cute.
哦，真聪明
Is that your dead husband's birthday?
那是你死鬼丈夫的生日吗？
Let me help you.
让我帮你
- Get him to the station. - You bet.
- 把他送到局里 - 没问题
Let me out.
放我出去
You know, Frank...
知道吗，弗兰克
...throwing you a tip now and again is one thing.
给你不时的递递消息是一回事
Password to the crime database et cetera, but letting you go?
给你犯罪数据库密码等等都行 可是放你走？
- Soap. - Fine.
- 舒布 - 好吧
How you doing?
你会怎么做？
Nineteen.
-19
Fuck!
操！
Fuck that...
操他妈的
What was that?
什么声音？
Go check it out.
去看看
What the fuck are you waiting for, Christmas?
你还在等什么，等耶稣吗？
Now.
现在
You, sit down.
你给我坐下
I'm calling this in.
我会叫我们的人赶来
Put your hands behind your back.
把手放背后
Goddamn it, Castle!
你个天杀的，卡洛斯！
Where do you think you're going?
你想去哪？
Castle!
卡洛斯！
I repeat, request immediate backup.
重复，请求紧急支援
Don'T worry, I'm here.
别担心，我来了
Give me your fucking gun.
把你的枪给我
Fuck!
操！
Stay right where you fucking are.
都他妈的给我别动
We did it, Budiansky, huh?
我们成功了，布迪安斯基，哈！
Would you mind explaining to me...
你介意给我解释下
...how a handcuffed criminal escapes custody...
一个双手被铐在后座的罪犯
...from the back of your locked car?
是怎么逃脱的吗？
That Castle's a slippery one.
那个卡塞尔太狡猾了
You'll be safe here.
你们在这儿很安全
We can manage on our own.
我们可以自己照顾自己
Just until we know Russoti's been arrested.
等罗塞蒂被捕后再说吧
Grace.
格雷斯
Grace, we're leaving soon, honey.
格雷斯，亲爱的，我们马上就走
She's smart.
她很漂亮
Go ahead. Open it.
没关系，打开吧
It belonged to my daughter.
这是我女儿的
Here.
给我
Put that down, honey.
把它放下，亲爱的
It...
这…
...was Lisa's favorite toy.
是莉萨最喜欢的玩具
She got so angry when her little brother used to hide it from her.
她的小弟弟把它藏起来时她可生气呢
Does she care if I play with it?
她会介意我玩这个吗？
No.
不会
You're gonna fry for killing two of my officers, Billy.
比利，你会为杀了两个警察坐上电椅的
- I want a lawyer. - Oh, you'll get your fucking lawyer.
- 我需要个律师 - 我会给你他妈的找律师
But no lawyer's gonna get you out of this one...
不过这次律师帮不了你
...you ugly piece of shit.
你这个肮脏的狗屎
Agent Miller, what are you doing here?
米勒特工，你来干什么？
Russoti.
是罗塞蒂
- What's he got to do with the bureau? - The case Donatelli was working on.
- 这和国土安全局有什么关系？ - 关于多纳特里的案子
He says he's got some intel, he wants to make a deal.
他说有重要情报，他想做笔交易
Anyone know where he is right now?
有人知道他现在在哪吗？
- Brought him into the observation room. - Good.
- 在监视室 - 很好
Yeah?
什么事？
Captain, Agent Miller from the bureau.
长官，我是国土安全局的米勒特工
I believe you were informed I'll be taking over this?
我想他们已经通知你我来接管这个案子
This perp killed two of my officers...
米勒，我希望你记住
...and terrorized the widow and child of one of your agents.
这个犯人杀了我们两位同事
You keep that in mind, Miller.
还挟持了你们一位特工的遗孀和小孩
You're lucky I came to you with this.
你该庆幸我找了你
That I'm a patriot.
因为我是个爱国者
Just like you.
和你一样
I shit red, white and blue.
我讨厌俄国人
The reason you came to me is because you got caught.
你找了我唯一原因是你被捕了
So don'T insult my intelligence, okay?
所以别侮辱我的智慧，好吗？
You tell me what you know.
你告诉我 你都知道些什么
If it's any good...
如果有用
...l'll recommend life without parole.
我会提议终身监禁不许保释
This deal is going down tonight.
那个交易今晚就会进行
I know when and I know where.
我知道时间和地点
So you're gonna give me and my brother here the immunity...
所以，要么给我和我兄弟特赦
...and the money...
还有钱
...or you're gonna have to explain to Wolf fucking Blitzer...
要么你去跟媒体解释下
...why you had the lead on the thing that killed half the fucking city...
为什么你明知道有东西会摧毁半座城市
...and you didn'T do a goddamn thing about it.
可却什么都没干
I'll be right back.
我出去一下
Oh, and Miller?
米勒
There's just one other little thing.
还有件小事
Happy?
高兴么？
Go, go, go.
行动，行动，行动
Get them alive.
抓活的
Homeland Security, put your weapons on the ground.
国土安全局，把武器丢地上
Do it now!
快点！
You're a fucking dead man.
你这个欠操的死定了
My father will kill you, you hear me?
我爸爸会杀了你，听到了吗？
My father will serve your head on a fucking silver platter.
他会把你脑袋放在银盘之里
Walk down to your right.
你们去右边
Stand clear.
人都散开
Agent Miller.
米勒特工
As agreed.
按照约定
The other condition of our agreement?
我们协议的其他条件呢？
Clear the area.
去四周搜下
I hope to God he finds you and you get what you deserve.
真希望他能找到你们，给你们应得的惩罚
- How long was l...? - A long time.
- 我睡了多长时间？ - 很长时间
- You should eat. - Grace.
- 该吃饭了 - 格雷斯
- What is it? - Egg and cheese...
- 这是什么？ - 鸡蛋、干酪
...MREs, that's all I have.
还有MRE，我只有这些
What's an MRE?
MRE是什么？
Meal ready-to-eat.
一种自热即时口粮
Military food. It's great for people who can'T cook.
军用食品，适合没法生火做饭的人
Look, Grace, this one came with Chuckles.
给你，格雷斯，这个味道不错
That's the best one to get.
是我这儿最好的
Not exactly a balanced breakfast.
这不是均衡早餐
Out of practice.
好久没吃了（那个了）
Not one more step.
站在那别动
- Where's Micro? - His mother isn'T feeling well.
- 迈克在哪？ - 他妈妈不太舒服
- He didn'T want to leave her. - Damn it.
- 他不想留她单独在家 - 见鬼
I need to talk to him.
我得和他谈谈
This is Carlos.
他是卡洛斯
He's...
他是…
...a friend of mine.
我的一位朋友
He's gonna hang while I take care of some things.
他会在我出去办事期间陪你们
- Hi, Carlos. I'm Grace. - Hey, little girl.
- 你好，卡洛斯，我叫格雷斯 - 你好，小姑娘
We're gonna be homeys, right?
我们会相处得很愉快，对吗？
Yeah, we're gonna be tight.
我们会是好朋友
This will all be over soon.
这一切很快会结束
Then you can go.
然后你们就能回家了
Don'T go.
别走
I need you alert.
我需要你时刻保持警惕
Don'T make me regret this.
别让我后悔托付了你
That was fun.
真好玩
Now, let's go kill Castle in his miserable hole.
现在我们去卡塞尔蜗居的洞里杀了他
No, not yet.
不，先别慌
We're gonna have ourselves a little bit of fun with this.
我们要让这件事更有趣
Next time he has to face us and a fucking army.
下次他就得面对我们和一大帮军队了
Where do we get the army from?
到哪儿找军队？
Just like Uncle Sam, bro.
就像山姆大叔一样，兄弟
We recruit in troubled neighborhoods.
我们去贫民区招兵
Offer a hundred grand towards a college education...
（山姆大叔）赞助他们十万块上大学
...they'll never get and promise nobody ever has to go to Iraq.
就不愁没人上伊拉克战场
Just as long as I get to kill Castle.
只要我能杀了卡塞尔
Don'T worry, brother, you will.
别急，兄弟，你会的
Just making damn sure this time he don'T come back breathing.
确保这次别让他再活过来
Here we have garlic, onion...
我们这儿有大蒜，洋葱
...a little paprika rub on a rare roast beef.
一点抹满胡椒粉的生牛肉
Hello, sports fans.
你好，球迷们
And how are you today, my friend?
今天怎么样，我的朋友？
Run! Get out of here!
跑！快离开这儿！
Hey.
嗨
I axed you a question.
我的斧头刚才问了你一个问题
Run!
快跑！
You don'T answer.
可你没回答
Guess I'll have to ax it again.
我猜它要再问一遍
Here I come.
我来了
Good.
很好
Bring them upstairs and meet me back down here.
把他们带上楼，然后回这儿和我碰头
Let's see if we can talk a few poor bastards into signing up.
看看我们能否说服些穷鬼接受我们的雇佣
Where are they?
他们在哪儿？
*
明天拂晓邓白氏酒店，你来交换你朋友 有条子，他们就死定了
I tried. I swear I tried.
我尽力了，我发誓我尽力了
Goddamn it.
可恶
Don'T die on me.
别死在我手里
I'm bleeding out.
我的血就要流尽了
I've seen this show before.
我以前在电影上看到过这种的情景
Shut up, kid.
别说话，老弟
You're gonna be fine.
你会没事的
It hurts real bad.
我痛得好辛苦
Hurts real bad, Frank.
真的很痛，弗兰克
Don'T let me die like this, man.
别让我死得这么辛苦
Not like this.
别这么痛苦
See you in hell.
我们在地狱见
I see you anywhere near hell...
不管我在地狱的哪儿见到你
...l'll kick your ass out.
我都会踢你的屁股，把你踢出去
I haven'T seen you in ages, Frank.
我们有好几年没见了，弗兰克
Whatever it is, it must be pretty bad.
不管（你来）是什么原因，一定是糟透了
Maybe I'm just here to see an old friend, Mike.
也许我只是来看位老朋友，麦克
Yeah, right.
是吧，也许吧
- I haven'T seen you since... - The funeral.
- 我们上次见面是在… - 在葬礼上
I know.
我还记得
I've been reading about you.
我听说了你的事
You've been a long a way from the seminary, my friend.
我的朋友，你已经很久没有亲近神了
I don'T even remember that as part of my life.
我都忘了它曾是我生活的一部分
Why do you do this?
为什么会这样？
Somebody has to punish the corrupt.
必须有人惩戒腐败
For in the same way you judge others, you will be judged.
别人会用你审判的方式来审判你
And with the measure you use, it will be measured to you.
别人也会用你的标准来衡量你
Matthew...
《马太福音》
...7:2.
第7章2节
I'm okay with that.
我记得很清楚
God be with you, Frank.
主与你同在，弗兰克
Sometimes I'd like to get my hands on God.
有时我想助神一臂之力
Interesting choice for a meeting place.
你选了个有趣的会面地点
I didn'T take you for a religious man, Castle.
我都不知道你还是个教徒，卡塞尔
Yeah, well...
是啊
...an eye for an eye. - Lf I remember right...
- 以眼还眼 - 如果我没记错…
...they're not called the Ten Suggestions.
《十诫》里可不提倡这样
Russoti's got Angela and Grace.
罗塞蒂抓了安琪和格雷斯
- How? - Doesn'T matter.
- 那又怎样？ - 你不在乎吗？
Maybe if you'd put them in protective custody like you should have...
也许如果你有保护好她们 像你该做的那样
...we wouldn'T be having this conversation.
我们就不会有这次谈话
They'd be dead.
她们会死的
The law can'T touch him, Castle.
法律对他束手无策，卡塞尔
Total immunity.
一点用都没有
Unless you've got a videotape of Russoti taking them.
除非你能拿到罗塞蒂劫持她们的录像
We can'T even give him a parking ticket.
不然我们连张停车罚单都没法开给他
It's a fucked-up system you're sworn to protect.
这就是你发誓保护的狗屁制度
Never said it was perfect.
没人说它是完美的
He wants me in exchange for them.
他想让我去交换她们
I need you to secure the trade.
我需要你来保证交易安全
Okay...
好吧
...but I'm doing this by the book.
但我不能执法犯法
What book do you think they're going by, huh?
你觉得他们会守什么法吗？
I took an oath, Castle.
我宣过誓，卡洛斯
- There are laws. - No official police procedure.
- 有法律 - （如果）不走正式的手续
You wanna come along?
你会一个人来吗？
Leave your badge at home.
把你的警徽留在家
- I have to think about it. - Clock's ticking.
- 我得考虑下 - 时间不等人
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
先生们，先生们
Relax.
放松点
We're looking for a few good men.
我们正在找一些好人
And we'd like to offer you the opportunity to be...
我们愿意提供给你们机会
...all that you can be.
做你们想做的任何事
Now, we've all suffered loss at the hands of The Punisher.
我们全在惩戒者手上吃够了苦头
And because we don'T look like everybody else...
因为我们看起来和其他人不同
...and because we don'T act like everybody else...
因为我们行事与众不同
...nobody does a goddamn thing about it.
我们并没做什么罪大恶极的事
Well, I say...
我告诉你们
...he ain'T the only one who can take the law into his own hands.
可不是只有他能自以为是的惩处别人
So if you're as sick of this cocksucker as I am...
所以如果你们也和我一样讨厌 这个婊子养的
...raise your armies.
拿起你们的武器
You'll be well-paid...
你们会得到丰厚的薪水
...you'll be well-armed...
优良的武器
...and at the end of it...
最后
...The Punisher will be dead.
惩戒者会被杀死
Agent Budiansky, just in time for happy hour.
布迪安斯基特工，正赶上欢乐时光 （注：指酒吧下午打折的时间段）
You need to come with me.
你跟我来
Where to?
去哪儿？
Your partner Frank Castle needs help.
你的伙伴弗兰克・卡塞尔需要帮助
"Partner" is a little bit of an exaggeration.
“伙伴”这词可真有点夸张
How did you know?
你怎么知道的？
Oh, usually, unless you've arrested Houdini...
通常，除非你抓的是哈里・胡迪尼 （注：以不可思议的套脱术闻名的魔术师）
...a handcuffed criminal does not escape that easily.
一个双手被铐上的犯人没那么容易逃脱
You know, you're not as stupid as you...
知道么，你可不像看起来那么笨
I didn'T say that.
当我没说
- Who are we looking for? - Cristu's father.
- 我们去找谁？ - 克里斯汀的父亲
I don'T think this is a good idea.
这可不是个好主意
What?
你说什么？
We're looking for Tiberiu. Cristu's father.
我们找帝贝柳，克里斯汀的父亲
- Why? - Lf I were Tiberiu...
- 做什么？ - 如果我是帝贝柳
...l'd probably wanna find the man...
我也许想找出那个害我儿子
...who was responsible for sending my son to prison for the rest of his life.
要在监狱度过余生的人
- And how would you do that? - I'd tell him when and where to find him.
- 你会怎么做呢？ - 我会告诉他在何时何地能找到他
What do you want from it?
你想要什么
I don'T like him and I want him taken care of.
我不喜欢他，想让你关照下他
No worries, my friend.
别担心，我的朋友
All right, lock and load. Lock and load.
好了，子弹上膛，拉拉枪栓
- Let's knock him down. - Get ready.
- 让我们好好教训他 - 准备好了
Here they are.
他们来了
Oh, boy.
哦，好家伙
Take it easy, James.
放松点，詹姆斯
He'll be here.
他马上到
- You get it. - Fuck that, man. You get it.
- 你去开门 - 他妈的，你去
I'll get it.
我去
- What you looking for? - I'm here to see the Jigsaw.
- 你找谁？ - 我们来找电锯的
You're out of luck. No Jigsaw here.
不好意思，这儿没有电锯
I'm here for The Punisher party.
我们来参加惩戒者的盛宴
Who's the old man?
那老头子是谁？
It's Cristu's father.
克里斯汀的父亲
Old-country genocidal maniac.
是个旧式的种族灭绝疯子
Figured he'd stir up a shit storm for us.
看来他会为我们制造场混乱
Cops will be all over this place once the fireworks start.
一旦有激烈的交火，警察就会包围这里
I wouldn'T worry about that.
别担心
I called in a explosives permit.
我申请了爆破许可
Construction crew. Said we'd be blasting dynamite all night.
我说我们工地上整晚都有爆破作业
So...
那么
...what's the plan?
你有什么计划？
I'm going in to get them.
我会杀进去救人
You call that a plan?
这就是你的计划？
It's all I need.
这就够了
Well, I'm going in with you.
好吧，我和你一起进去
Never took the time to think about where I was headed.
我从不费功夫去想会被（命运）带到哪儿
I'm far down that road.
那不是我做事的方式
You're not going there.
你哪儿都去不了
Thanks, Frank.
谢了，弗兰克
You know he's gonna take it out on me when he wakes up.
你不知道他醒了会拿我出气吗？
If you don'T hear gunfire for longer than five minutes...
如果枪声停了5分钟以上
...the girls are not here, set him loose.
那俩女孩还没出来，把他弄醒
Come on, get him. Go, go, go.
给我上，向他开火，快点
Quiet, fool.
小声点，蠢货
It's time.
是时候了
James, be careful.
詹姆斯，小心点
Oh, for fuck's sake.
喔，见他妈的鬼
Won'T be replacing that son of yours any time soon.
你再不能生儿子了
Blood in the urine. Early indicator of kidney failure.
尿血，肾衰竭早期症状
You should be seeing double right about now.
你现在应该出现重影了
That would be a torn meniscus.
那大概是半月板撕裂的声音吧
- James. - Gun.
- 詹姆斯 - 给我枪
Welcome, welcome, welcome.
欢迎，欢迎，欢迎
Mom.
妈
- Please, help us. - Shut the fuck up.
- 求你了，救救我们 - 给我闭嘴
Come on, Castle.
来吧，卡塞尔
Don'T be shy.
别害羞
Throw down your gun.
放下你的枪
- Die, you bastard. - No.
- 去死，王八蛋 - 不
James, that's no way to punish The Punisher.
詹姆斯，这可不是惩戒惩戒者的方法
Nice shooter.
是把好枪
Catch.
拿着
Let's play a game, what do you say?
我们来玩个游戏怎么样？
You got one round left in there.
你枪里只有一颗子弹
You shoot one of these two.
你开枪杀了他们中的一个
I'll let the other one go free.
我就放另一个走
What do you say, Frank?
怎么样，弗兰克？
Who's it to be, your fat friend right here?
你选哪一个，是这边这位胖朋友？
Or that nice little piece of jailbait over there?
还是那边那位漂亮的祸水妞？
Burn in hell.
下地狱吧！
Okay, then they both die.
好吧，那他们都得死
Frank.
弗兰克
She's a kid.
她还是个孩子
Shoot me.
杀了我吧
Okay, fuck it. Kill her first.
好吧，先杀了她
- No. - Stop.
- 不 - 住手
He's made a decision.
他已经做了决定
Not looking too good for you, fatso.
看起来对你不利，胖子
After three, Castle.
我数三声，卡塞尔
One.
一
Two.
二
You won'T feel a thing, Micro.
你不会感到痛的，迈克
Three.
三
God...
天哪…
Frank.
弗兰克
Get out.
快出去
Fuck you.
操你
Let me put you out of my misery.
你来结束我的痛苦吧
This is just the beginning.
这才是开始
You okay?
你没事吧？
- Where's Castle? - Still inside.
- 卡塞尔在哪儿？ - 还在里面
And Micro?
迈克呢？
Frank.
弗兰克
Frank, are you okay?
弗兰克，你没事吧？
You better get out of here.
你最好快离开这儿
Yeah. Come on, Frank, I'll buy you a drink.
没错，快走，弗兰克，我可以请你喝一杯
Wait.
等等
My husband...
我丈夫…
...Nicky.
尼基
We talked about you.
我们聊起过你
Argued about you.
讨论过你
He said you were one of the good guys.
他说你是个好人
You know, buddy.
知道吗，朋友
Maybe it's time to quit now, huh?
也许现在是时候离开了，唔？
I mean, you must get tired of this, right?
我是说，你一定感到厌倦了，是吗？
And I think you got all the criminals in town.
我觉得你已经把城里的罪犯抓遍了
If there are any left...
如果还有剩下的
...they ought to at least consider rehabilitation.
他们应该至少考虑下改邪归正
I mean, contrary to popular belief, people can change.
我是说，和主流观点相反 我相信人是会变的
I guess what I'm saying is...
我想我的意思是…
...l'm just personally not a fan of the death penalty.
我个人并不崇尚死刑
Frank?
弗兰克
Where did he go?
你去哪儿了？
Hey.
嗨
Give me your fucking wallet, motherfucker.
把你的钱包交出来，傻B
You're kidding, right?
你开玩笑吗？
Do I look like I'm fucking kidding?
我看起来像他妈的开玩笑吗？
Frank.
弗兰克
Give me your wallet.
把钱包交出来
- Frank. - Do you wanna die?
- 弗兰克 - 你想死吗？
For the last time, give me your wallet.
最后一次，把钱包给我
Oh, God. Now I've got brain splattered all over me.
哦，天哪，脑浆溅了我一身